<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Big Ambitions Foundation - &#34;Launching on 4th January 2016&#34; </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Big Ambitions Foundation - &#34;Launching on 4th January 2016&#34; </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Nitin Agarwal&#34; style=&#34;float:center;width:681px;height:410px;&#34;&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-us:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;About Us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Ambitions is a nonprofit organisation dedicated to the sharing of knowledge and latest updates about Open source Cloud, SDN / NFV and Networking technologies on a common platform by organising free meetups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Ambitions helps talented and passionate newcomers build their career in Open source, Linux, Cloud, SDN / NFV, Networking by providing comprehensive, practical and certified training at no cost to women and at an affordable fees to the students worldwide. The goal of the Big Ambitions Foundation is to bridge the gap between Open Source and Women, encouraging them to contribute upstream and be in link with the larger community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Ambitions feature news, updates, research and anaylsis of the open source technologies by performing data research to show how the new open source technologies would affect the enterprises, startups and businesses worlwide and help them choose the right stack of open source technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-vision:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Our Vision&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Ambitions, a nonprofit organisation has been founded to serve some of the important aspects in Open Source world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide a common platform to share knowledge and lastest updates on the Open source technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help talented and passionate newcomers build their career in Open source, Linux, Cloud, SDN / NFV and Networking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bridge the gap between open source and women.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Encourage students and women in technology to get involved in open source and contribute to the upstream.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help the enterprises, startups and the businesses worldwide choose the right stack of open source technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-mission:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Our Mission&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Ambitions Foundation mission includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Featuring around 1000 tutorials and articles on our focused open source technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysing and performing data research to show how these new open source technologies would affect the enterprises, startups and the businesses worldwide.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing comprehensive, practical and certified training on our focused open source rechnologies to around 1000 women worldwide at no cost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing training to students worldwide at an affordable fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organising regular meetups worldwide to share knowledge and latest updates on our focused open source technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interviews with Open source developers and passionate women in open source technology to feature it in our Spotlight page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-spotlight-feature:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Our Spotlight feature&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Spotlight feature includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interviews with the Open source developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New features and tools launched at the Open source conferences / summits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interviews with the passionate women in Open source technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interviews with the startups following our Research / Analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;founding-members:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Founding Members&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for Founding Members / Sponsors to join our nonprofit organisation and help us in achieving our mission. All the Founding members must commit some financial support as well as provide access to their office for conducting free meetups and training sessions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your company is interested in becoming a Founding Member at Big Ambitions Foundation, Please let us know via email to info@bigambitions.org.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;advisory-board-at-big-ambitions:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Advisory Board at Big Ambitions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Ambitions would be governed on the policies decided by our Board of Advisors council. Our Board of Advisors includes one member from each of the founding members / sponsors, founder of Big Ambitions and respected experienced persons from the open source world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;focused-technologies:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Focused technologies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Ambitions would be currently focusing on Open Soure Cloud, SDN / NFV and Networking technologies mainly Linux systems (Ubuntu, RHEL, CentOS), OpenStack, OpenDaylight, Docker and Linux containers, Flocker, Kubernetes, Mesos, OpenShift, Clair, Weave, Vagrant, Puppet, Deis, Flannel, Project Atomic, Totem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More technologies to be added soon in future!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefit-to-the-open-source-world:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Benefit to the Open Source world&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our training sessions, we would be encouraging the participants to contribute upstream and get involved with the larger community. This would help the open source technologies to have more contributions and in effect will increase the number of people with open source experience in the market for the companies to hire open source talent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, our foundation would be working to bridge the gap between Open source and women by offering training to women at no cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would also be conducting free meetups worldwide to share knowledge and latest updates about the Open source technologies which would help the people and newbies in the open source world to enhance their skills as well as learn new skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefit-to-the-users:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Benefit to the Users&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Passionate Women would be having the opportunity to get certified training on the Open source technologies at no cost and hence can make their career in Cloud Computing, SDN / NFV, Linux and Networking. Students have the opportunity to get training at an affordable price, cheap from the market price. Participants would be provided with certificates on the successful completion of the training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefit-to-the-startups-and-enterprises:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Benefit to the Startups and Enterprises&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team would be performing data research and analysis of the open source technologies, and will publish it on our website as well as our social media presence which would help the startups, enterprises and the businesses worldwide to choose the right stack of open source technologies for building their product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;big-ambitions-presence-at-open-source-conferences-summits:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Big Ambitions presence at Open Source Conferences / Summits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Ambitions team would also be presenting and submitting talks at various Open Source conferences / summits namely OpenStack Summit, OpenDaylight Summit, OSCON, LinuxCon, Mesoscon, ContainerCon, DockerCon, Container Days, DevOps Summit, Red Hat Summit and others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-us:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to contact us for any suggestion, feedback, enquiry or sponsorship, Please feel free to drop us an email to info@bigambitions.org.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;share-this-page-via:b9bcf8cb73ce4a081a635ad7c0acd9dd&#34;&gt;Share this Page via:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;a2a_kit a2a_kit_size_32 a2a_default_style&#34;&gt;
&lt;a class=&#34;a2a_button_twitter&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&#34;a2a_button_facebook&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&#34;a2a_button_linkedin&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&#34;a2a_button_google_plus&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&#34;a2a_button_email&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;text/javascript&#34; src=&#34;//static.addtoany.com/menu/page.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;


&lt;link href=&#34;//cdn-images.mailchimp.com/embedcode/slim-081711.css&#34; rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
&lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
    #mc_embed_signup{background:#1E90FF; clear:left; font:18px Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif;  width:700px;}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div id=&#34;mc_embed_signup&#34;&gt;
&lt;form action=&#34;//bigambitions.us12.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=efeb8b0f151453b6bb77cf67b&amp;amp;id=079580c475&#34; method=&#34;post&#34; id=&#34;mc-embedded-subscribe-form&#34; name=&#34;mc-embedded-subscribe-form&#34; class=&#34;validate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; novalidate&gt;
    &lt;div id=&#34;mc_embed_signup_scroll&#34;&gt;
    &lt;label for=&#34;mce-EMAIL&#34;&gt;Subscribe to our Newsletter&lt;/label&gt;
    &lt;input type=&#34;email&#34; value=&#34;&#34; name=&#34;EMAIL&#34; class=&#34;email&#34; id=&#34;mce-EMAIL&#34; placeholder=&#34;email address&#34; required&gt;
    &lt;div style=&#34;position: absolute; left: -5000px;&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;input type=&#34;text&#34; name=&#34;b_efeb8b0f151453b6bb77cf67b_079580c475&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34; value=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;clear&#34;&gt;&lt;input type=&#34;submit&#34; value=&#34;Subscribe&#34; name=&#34;subscribe&#34; id=&#34;mc-embedded-subscribe&#34; class=&#34;button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/form&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>